

# LY THANH LONG FRONT-END DEVELOPER

**4** 07/01/2001

lythanhlong.fetel.hcmu s@gmail.com

Thich Buu Dang Street,
Ward 1, District Go Vap,
HCMC

**\** 0813384430

With about 2 years of experience working with HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJS and related frameworks such as ReactJS, I have successfully developed web applications and improved effective project management through Scrum, Agile practices. I bring responsibility, dynamism and focus, driving collaboration and communication to develop web and mobile solutions.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **ELECTRONICS AND TELECOMMUNICATIONS**

**VNUHCM - University of Science** 

09/2019 - 07/2023

GPA: 7.0

## **SKILLS**

#### Front-End

- 2 years experience with Reactjs, NextJS and 1 year Laravel, Wordpress.
- Proficient in HTML/CSS/SASS, jQuery, Ajax, PHP, JavaScript, TypeScript, NodeJS.
- Knowledge of Webpack: NPM, Yarn and other library UI build tools
- Familiarity with Web API, Web Services REST, SOAP, XML.
- Knowledge of UX/UI design principles

#### Back-End

NodeJS, Python

#### **Databases**

MongoDb, MySQL, PostgreSQL

#### **Others**

- Strong problem solving, debugging skills and photoshop
- Excellent communication and collaboration skills
- Familiarity with Agile and Scrum processes
- Ability to create unit tests for web applications
- Knowledge of code versioning tools such as Github, Gitlab.
- Good written and spoken English.

# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

#### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

ADS AGENCY 2/2024 - Present

- Develop TrueAds project using Agile method to build a CRM system for about 50 businesses, helping website performance increase by 15%.
- Develop prototypes and mockups for new features, enhancing consumer UI/UX experience.
- Integrate websites with Facebook API services to enhance user experience, increase engagement, automate message replies and comments features, and analyze sales data for Weilaya, Layender and 50 more.

#### JUNIOR FRONT-END ENGINEER

TRANIZI | 2/2023 - 1/2024

- Developed and maintained front-end code for Microlearning platform, serving multiple countries using React.js and Redux.
- Implement responsive designs and mobileoptimized UI/UX.
- Collaborate with the backend team to integrate RESTful APIs and ensure seamless data flow.
- Improve site performance by implementing code optimization, which reduces load times by 30%.
- Contributed to the development of customer dashboards, providing real-time data analysis and visualization capabilities.

# **ACTIVITIES**

#### UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE ESPORT CLUB

Head of the University of Science Esport Club.

09/2020 - 12/2022

Organize e-sports tournaments for students inside and outside the school.

## **REFERENCES**

#### **NGUYEN MANH TIEN**

CTO - CellphoneS, Founder InsightLab , CTO TRAINIZI

Phone: 0909654069

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### **INSIGHT LAB** 9/2021 - 8/2022

- Execute projects related to Chrome extensions.
- Design web applications based on highly responsive user interfaces to sell Chrome extensions.
- Build reusable components and Front-End libraries for future use

# **PROJECTS**

#### TRUEADS 2/2024 - Present

#### **Description:**

 The software helps you turn Facebook conversations into orders. Comprehensive sales solution, maximum order conversion rate and sales consultation, quick comment processing, automatic chat with customers.

Members: 2 members

**Technologies:** HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Wordpress, PHP, Ajax, CI/CD, AWS, facebook APIs documentation.

#### Responsibilities:

- Design mindmap, Jira and database for the project.
- Deploy a database to operate, manage and collect statistics about customers and orders.
- UX/UI design to ensure user interface meets design requirements and specifications.

**Link product:** https://trueads.vn/

#### **TRAINZI** 2/2023 - 1/2024

#### **Description:**

 Trainizi - All-in-one training tool with Gamification & Al | Trainizi is an interactive microlearning platform designed to help organizations train, engage and retain their deskless and officeless workforce with 3x return on investment.

#### Members: 4 members

• **Technologies**: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Reactjs, Tailwind, Typescript, Next.JS, Node.JS, Redux, yarn, Websocket, Rechart, Restful APIs.

#### Responsibilities:

- Develop responsive and user-friendly web interfaces for both learners and instructors using the ReactJS frontend framework.
- Test and troubleshoot interface issues and debug applications.
- Collaborate with backend developers to ensure smooth integration between frontend and backend components.
- Design UX/UI to ensure the user interface meets requirements and design specifications.
- Build reusable components and Front-End libraries for future use.

Link product: <a href="https://trainizi.com/">https://trainizi.com/</a>

# THESIS SEMINAR: SYSTEM MANAGEMENT FANPAGE FACEBOOK

1/7/2022 - 20/7/2022

#### **Description:**

 The school club introduction website allows searching for members, club presentation, and tracking club posts through the use of Graph API technology.

Members: 2 members

#### **Technologies:**

 HTML, CSS, bootstrap, JavaScript, Jquery, PHP, Laravel, MySQL.

#### Responsibilities:

- Design the website interface and implement post filters.
- Connect to a MySQL database.
- Use Facebook's Graph API to synchronize post data from the fanpage to MySQL and display data on the website interface.